Agents may be intelligent, but there's
some information they simply don't have.
A new version of an open source library
created after their training run, the
way your team decided how to use a
certain framework, or the broader
company policies they have to abide by.
Ensuring agents receive the information
they need isn't easy. You're relying on
their random decision to seek
information instead of hallucinating an
answer, which often doesn't work, and to
do so within their limited memory.
To top that, agents are changing rapidly
and new ones get released every week,
making it hard to support all the agents
your team is using. Tesla spec registry
solves this by making this information a
part of your software project. It
contains packages of specs which are
added to your project just like software
dependencies. The specs are available
for any agent developing this app and
designed to be easily consumed and
applied by agents. The content of these
spec packs can be any context your agent
needs and isn't in your code. This
ranges from instructions and examples
for using open source libraries through
reusable workflows for common tasks like
adding analytics or fixing security
issues to your specific practices and
policies. All information the agent
needs to know to do its job properly.
Tesla's spec registry already contains
over 10,000 usage specs for popular open
source libraries. These specs make it
clear how the agent should use this
library based on deep analysis and real
world usage data, accelerating
development and minimizing mistakes.
Usage specs are versioned to match the
library version, keeping the agent
effective even when you're using a very
new or a very old library. Tesla's spec
registry is now available in beta and
it's free to use.